Guide to the Rice University Historic Clothing collection, 1916-2017 UA 392
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Historic Clothing collection
1916-2017
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University.
UA 392
56 Linear Feet 64 boxes and hanging storage
This collection contains costumes worn at Archi-Arts Ball, Freshmen beanies, Rice cheerleading uniforms, athletic sweaters, uniforms, club and program t-shirts, from various campus-wide events.
Historical Note
Rice University was founded in 1891 and opened in 1912. The clothing in this collection reflects many of the events and trends over the years from the Academic regalia of the first female graduate, Miss H. Lel Red in 1916, freshman beanies, cheerleading uniforms, costumes for the Archi-Arts ball to more recent t-shirts for campus-wide events and programs.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains costumes worn at Archi-Arts Ball, Freshmen beanies, Rice cheerleading uniforms, athletic sweaters, uniforms, club and program t-shirts, from various campus-wide events.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research. Boxes 2 and 5 stored onsite at the Woodson Research Center. Boxes 1, 3, 4, and 6-63 stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Clothing for this collection was taken both from the Association of Rice Alumni Collection (UA003) and the Rice University Memorabilia Collection (UA225)
Index Terms
Subjects
Social life and customs; Rice University -- History; Athletics; Universities and colleges; Women
Document Types
memorabilia
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University.
- Series I: Archi-Arts Costumes
  - "Goddess of the Hunt," worn by Christine Pope, 1932 (Box 1)
  - "Envy." worn by Beverly Taylor Maurice--"Emotion" was the theme, 1946 (Box 1)
  - "Cuba Libre" dress worn by Dorothy Lottman; Includes pictures and foam-core descriptions for display [Oversized Box], 1944 (Box 2)
  - Bronze dress worn by Marilyn Marris; includes pictures and foam-core descriptions for display [Oversized Box], 1950 (Box 2)
  - "Titania" Gown worn by Doris Moellenberndt [Oversized Box], 1948 (Box 3)
  - "Titania" Crown worn by Doris Moellenberndt, 1948 (Box 4)
  - Titania Wings and Wand worn by Doris Moellenberndt [Oversized Box], 1948 (Box 5)
  - "Crime", Black Satin outfit and fishnet worn by Nancy Moore Eubank; Includes photo, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Purple Velvet and Tapestry Gown worn by Joy Kenter Holland (Oversize Hanging Clothes Storage)
- Series II: Military
  - Green metal helmet with figure of Rice owl on top with words "The Warrior-Onward" & "Excuse My Dust" (Box 7)
  - John H. Meyer Jr.'s Lt. USNR USS Brown hat (Box 7)
  - Student Army Training Corps Uniform: Jacket, pants, shirt, belt, 1 pr. Puttees, hat belonging to Wade Mount '22, 1918 (Box 8)
  - White WWI Sailor Suit given by Sarah Lane, 1917-1918 (Box 8)
  - Women's WWI Army Uniform skirt and jacket belonging to Anna Schirmer Vilbig '20, 1918 (Box 9)
  - V-12 uniform of D.C. McLeaish (Box 9)
  - Women's Army Uniform skirt and jacket, with 1 pr. Woman's Army Boots (Box 9)
  - 2 Women's Army Uniforms and Jackets (Box 10)
  - Collar button from Women's Army Uniform, 1917-1918 (Box 10)
  - Woman's ROTC Uniform donated by Lt. André Carter, May 26, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Woman's ROTC uniform (Box 11)
- Series III: Regalia
  - Academic Hoods (Box 12)
    - Hardin Craig - Princeton
    - Hardin Craig, Jr. - Harvard
    - 2 Rice University - B.A.
    - Haverford College - B.A.
    - Pacific University - M.A.
    - Cornell University - Ph.D.
    - Emory University - Ph.D.
    - University of Michigan - Ph.D.
    - Ohio State University - Ph.D. (Dr. Houston's)
    - Carolyn Foulkes Morrison, '35, 1935
    - Blue Silk Sample Hood, with name Hugh Scott Cameron
  - Academic Caps (Box 13)
    - Cap of Edith Lessman, 1914
    - Cap of Thomas T. Holloway, Ph. D
    - 4 large Marshall's Medieval Hats, one belonging to H.E. Rorschach, Jr, Presnted by J.W. Sims, August 22, 63
    - 5 small Marshall's Medieval hats presented by J. W. Sims, August 22, 1963
    - Black Tassle - from John W. Lainer (Alumni Affairs), 1966
    - White Tassle belonging to Dr. Tom Holloway '66, 1966
    - 4 tassels, 1966
  - Academic gown of Miss H. Lel Red, 1916 (Box 14)
  - Richard Smalley Academic Regalia (1 robe, 4 hoods), August 1, 2012 (Oversize Hanging Clothes Storage)
    Separated Materials
    Added to the Rice Historic Clothing Collection from 2012.UA032 Richard Smalley Academic Regalia Accession
  - Thomas T. Holloway, Ph. D Academic Regalia (Oversize Hanging Clothes Storage)
  - Two Hugh Scott Cameron blue academic regalia stoles (Box 14)
  - Black Doctoral Robe with blue trim; black hood with blue trim and a shell with lilac and silver stripes (Box 14)
  - Black cap and gown with blue and gray satin and velvet doctoral degree hood (Box 15)
  - Bright Red Academic Robe with yellow trim; black hood with purple trim and a shell with orange and black stripes (Box 16)
  - Pale Maroon Doctoral Robe with black trim; black hood with a bright red shell. (Box 17)
- Series IV: Cheerleading and Dance
  - Cheerleading Sweaters
    - Jane & Joan Ryba cheerleader sweaters, gray with blue "R" (Box 18)
    - Jane & Joan Ryba cheerleader sweaters, white with blue "R" (Box 18)
    - Cheerleader sweater belonging to Albert Kidd, 1962-1963 (Box 19)
    - Cheerleader sweater & photos belonging to Mary Ann Kopriva, 1956 (Box 20)
    - 2 Cheerleader sweaters owned by Hatwin Moore (Box 21)
    - White Cheerleader Sweater owned by Carolyn Dearmond '58, 1958 (Box 22)
    - Gray Cheerleading sweater owned by Carolyn Dearmond '58, 1958 (Box 22)
  - Cheerleader's jacket belonging to Jerry Dobelman, 1942 (Box 23)
  - 2 Cheerleading Uniform tops owned by Carloyn Dearmond '58, 1958 (Box 24)
  - White Cheerleading jumpsuit owned by Carolyn Dearmond '58, 1958 (Box 24)
  - Jane Ryba head cheerleader outfit (white skirt and white and blue shirt), 1955 (Box 25)
  - Jane & Joan Ryba cheerleader outfit (white and blue shirt, wool) (Box 26)
  - Jane & Joan Ryba cheerleader skirts (Box 27)
  - Natalie Ashcroft's Cheerleader's Uniform; Disk with Cheer-leading pictures donated by Natalie Ashcroft, 2007 (Box 28)
  - Cheerleader's uniform and pompoms (Box 28)
  - Rice Dance Team Uniforms (Box 29)
- Series V: Athletics
  - Athletic Sweaters
    - "R" sweater owned by JiLee Vilbig, 1920 (Box 30)
    - Track sweater owned by J. Lonnie Thomas; lettered in Track (Javelin) 1923 Junior, donated by wife, Shirley Cowan Thomas, 1927 (Box 30)
    - Track sweater owned by J. Lonnie Thomas; lettered in Track (Javelin) 1924 Senior donated by wife, Shirley Cowan Thomas, 1927 (Box 30)
    - Navy Rice athletic sweater owned by Fred Stancliff '26, 1926 (Box 31)
    - Gray Rice athletic sweater owned by Fred Stancliff '26, 1926 (Box 31)
    - Gray Rice athletic sweater owned by Fred Stancliff '26, 1926 (Box 31)
    - Track sweater owned by Larry Hamilton '29, 1929 (Box 32)
    - Track sweater owned by Larry Hamilton '29, 1929 (Box 32)
    - Baseball Sweater owned by Howard Hegel, 1940 (Box 32)
    - Football sweater (donated by Edward Kelley, Jr.), "Fitch" on label (Box 33)
    - Football Sweater, "Thomas" on label (Box 33)
    - Tennis Sweater, 1929 (Box 33)
  - Fred Hansen '63 track uniform worn at 1964 Tokyo Olympics where he won gold medal in pole vaulting (Box 34)
  - T. Washington #15 Football Jersey in white with Navy decals and grey trim, and a patch reading "Celebrating Excellence SWC 1914-1996" (Box 35)
  - "La Rocca" #7 Football Jersey in blue with white decals and grey trim, and a patch reading "Celebrating Excellence SWC 1914-1996" (Box 35)
  - 3 athletic shirts owned by Fred Stancliff '26, 1926 (Box 35)
  - Charles Parker Practice Jersey, 1940s (Box 35)
  - Rice Lacrosse Team Jersey (Box 35)
  - Football Jersey (Box 35)
  - Football jersey #98 (Box 35)
  - Football Jacket (leather) (Oversize Hanging Clothes Storage)
  - Football letter jacket (Box 36)
  - Football Jacket (Box 36)
  - Athletics Uniforms
    - White "Rice 42" Baseball shirt (Box 37)
    - White "Rice 32" Baseball shirt (Box 37)
    - White mesh "Rice" sleeveless athletics shirt (Box 37)
    - Blue mesh "Rice 43" sleeved athletics shirt (Box 37)
    - Blue mesh "Rice R" sleeved athletics shirt (Box 37)
    - Blue "Rice" sleeved athletics shirt (Box 37)
    - Blue "Rice" sleeveless athletics jersey (Box 37)
    - Grey "23" sleeveless athletics jersey (Box 37)
    - Blue "Rice" sleeveless basketball jersey (Box 37)
    - Grey "Owls 41" sleeveless basketball jersey (Box 37)
    - 2 pairs of mesh athletic shorts (blue and white) (Box 37)
    - 2 pairs of basketball shorts (blue and white) (Box 37)
    - White Football Pants (Box 37)
    - White basketball break-away pants and shirt for warm-ups (Box 38)
    - Blue basketball break-away pants and shirt for warm-ups (Box 38)
    - Rice Volleyball blue windbreaker and pants (Box 38)
    - Rice Volleyball blue windbreaker and pants (Box 38)
    - Wrestling singlet (Box 38)
    - Rice Physical Education shorts, n.d. (Box 38)
  - Athletics Merchandise
    - White with blue strip mesh "Rice" tank top (Box 38)
    - White mesh "Rice" tank top (Box 38)
    - Blue SWC basketball sweater (Box 38)
    - Blue "13" Polo with collar and long sleeves (Box 38)
    - Blue "Rice 7" Polo with collar and long sleeves (Box 38)
    - Black Rice Basketball polo shirt (Box 38)
    - Rice Texas Bowl comemmorative towel, December 30, 2008 (Box 38)
- Series VI: Hats
  - Round felt hat worn by F.W. Vessey, 1929 (Box 39)
  - Freshmen beanies, '25; '27; '30 (2); '33; '34; '35 (2); '45; '52 (2); '53; '55 (2); '56; '58 (2); '60; '64; '65; '66; '68; '72 (2); one blue/gray, no date (Box 40)
  - Green Slime Beanie in case (Box 41)
  - Baseball caps and visors (Box 42)
    - Sports-related hats
      - College World Series baseball hat, 2003
      - College World Series baseball hat, 2006
      - "Beat the Aggies" hats (2)
      - 2003 NCAA Baseball Division I National Champions hats (2 tan w/ blue text, 1 tan w/ black text, 1 white with grey text)
      - Amon G. Carter Stadium hat
    - Event-related hats
      - Signed RICE visors (2), 1996
      - 3 Richard E. Smalley and Robert E Curl, Jr. 1996 Nobel Prize in Chemistry commemoration hats (1 signed)
      - "Rice University 100 Years" Centennial hat
      - Rice Football 100th Season hat
      - Brown "Homecoming 1998" hat
      - Blue "Homecoming 1999" hat
      - Blue "Opening Day 2000"
      - 2 Gray "Homecoming 2000" hats
      - "Have a Rice Christmas 2013" hat
    - Rice Hats--general
      - Rice logo camouflage hat
      - Gray "Rice" hat
      - White "Rice R" hat
      - Owl logo hats, gray (2)
      - Rice seal hat, blue (2)
      - Rice hat, army green
      - Rice Business hat
      - "Raising Spirits for Rice Athletics" hat
      - "Beat A(R)my" hat
      - Rice Texas U.S. Flag Hat
    - Bucky Allshouse Rice Baseball Cap Collection (Box 43)
  - Generic Rice Hats (Box 43a)
    - Rice Straw Cowboy Hat (Box 43a)
    - Rice Pom Pom Beanie (Box 43a)
    - Tan baseball cap with 1950s version Rice owl, n.d. (Box 43a)
- Series VII: Sweaters and Jackets
  - White Rice Sweatshirt owned by Fred Stancliff '26 (Box 44)
  - White Rice Sweatshirt owned by Fred Stancliff '26, 1926 (Box 44)
  - White Rice undershirt owned by Fred Stancliff '26 (Box 44)
  - White Rice undershirt owned by Fred Stancliff '26 (Box 44)
  - Blue/gray Rice sweater owned by Fred Stancliff '26 (Box 44)
  - Gray Rice tank top owned by Fred Stancliff '26 (Box 44)
  - Tan Rice tank top owned by Fred Stancliff '26 (Box 44)
  - Sweater owned by Fred Stancliff '26 (Box 44)
  - Woman's blue flannel blazer owned by Janet Blair Hargrove '28, 1928 (Box 45)
  - Blue Blazer, 1928 (Box 45)
  - Sweater owned by Florence Powers Stancliff '29 (Box 45)
  - Red Bale football sweater, 1930s (Box 45)
  - Sweater owned by Bill Bishop (Box 45)
  - Gray sweater with Blue "R" owned by Wendell Ley (Box 46)
  - White sweater with blue "R" owned by Wendell Ley (Box 46)
  - Jacket owned by Hallie Beth Poindexter (Box 46)
  - Blue and brown striped sweater donated by Anna Schirmer Vilbig (Box 46)
  - White sweater owned by RJ Williams (Box 47)
  - Quarterback Club sweater (Box 47)
  - Houston-Tenneco Marathon Graphic Jacket (Box 47)
  - White Rice Lab Coat, "Karrin" Embroidered on front pocket" (Oversize Hanging Clothes Storage)
  - Black Will Rice Blazer, 1960s (Oversize Hanging Clothes Storage)
    Moved from Rice University Will Rice College Records
    General
    Worn primarily by men's chorus members during the 1960s
  - Black Baker College Blazer (Oversize Hanging Clothes Storage)
- Series VIII: Dresses and Skirts
  - 1st Rondelet queen's dress belonging to Sara Meredith, 1947 (Box 48)
  - Freshman women's Pinafore belonging to Sarah Meredith '47 (Box 49)
  - Freshman dress belonging to Nancy Moore Eubank, 1951 (Box 50)
  - Nancy Thornall Burch '61 black wool pleated plaid skirt, 1961 (Box 50)
  - Black Dress (Box 50)
  - Red Dress (Box 50)
  - Freshman Women's Pinafore (Oversize Hanging Clothes Storage)
- Series IX: T-shirts
  - Rice Club/Organization T-shirts
    - NASA History Team t-shirt, 1986 (Box 51)
    - S.O.A.P (Students Organized Against Rape) "No Means No" T-shirt, 1992 (Box 51)
    - Student Admission Council T-Shirt, ca. 2000 (Box 51)
    - National Hispanic Institute t-shirt, 2001 (Box 51)
    - The Hoot "Feeding hungry students since 2010", n.d. (Box 51)
    - South Asian Society - Dhamaka, 2011 (Box 51)
    - South Asian Society - (Desi)rable, 2011-2012 (Box 51)
    - "Building Rice Academics In Neuroscience" t-shirt (Box 51)
    - Campanile t-shirt, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Coffee House t-shirt, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Habitat for Humanity (Rice Chapter) t-shirt (Box 51)
    - Rice Hebrew T-shirt, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Native American Student Association - Pow Wow, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Nocturnals (Rice Vocal Ensemble) T-Shirt, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Outdoors Club t-shirt with spider, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Outdoors Club t-shirt, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Peer Academic Advising
      - "Hello I'm an O-Week PAA" t-shirt, n.d. (Box 51)
      - Peer Academic Advising, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Philharmonics t-shirt, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Rice Student Volunteer Program
      - "Pancakes for Parkinsons," sponsored by RSVP t-shirt, April 14, 2012 (Box 51)
      - Fall Outreach Day (RSVP) T-Shirt, n.d. (Box 51)
      - Rice "X" and "Ten Years" t-shirt for Rice Student Volunteer Program (Box 51)
      - Blue t-shirt RSVP with a black hand (Box 51)
      - White "RSVP" t-shirt, n.d. (Box 51)
      - White RSVP t-shirt with colorful hands graphic (Box 51)
    - Rice Sailing t-shirt, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Thresher t-shirt, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Young Democrats t-shirt, n.d. (Box 51)
  - Event T-shirts
    - Dated Single Event T-shirts
      - Economics Summit Volunteer t-shirt, 1990 (Box 52)
      - Weiss Jazz Night "We are that!" t-shirt, February 12, 1994 (Box 52)
      - Southern Conference on Women's History t-shirt, 1994 (Box 52)
      - Weiss College presents: Jamfest t-shirt, 1994 (Box 52)
      - Baker Institute for Public Policy "Foreign Policy Challenges" t-shirt, 1995 (Box 52)
      - Elton John / Billy Joel concert "Face to Face" t-shirt, 1995 (Box 52)
      - Weiss Tabletop: "Hello Hamlet" t-shirt, March 21-23, 27-29, 1996 (Box 52)
      - Baker Institute for Public Policy "Domestic Policy at the End of the Century" t-shirt, 1996 (Box 52)
      - Weiss College presents: Jamfest Acapalooza t-shirt, 1997 (Box 52)
      - Archi-Arts t-shirt, February 19, 2000 (Box 52)
      - Archi-Arts t-shirt, 2001 (Box 52)
      - Team Weiss Big Bang, 2002 (Box 52)
      - SWNT Growth Mechanism Workshop, 2003 (Box 52)
      - "Small is really big!" Building the world's largest nanotube model t-shirt, April 22, 2005 (Box 52)
      - NASA and Rice University Growth Mechanisms Workshop, 2005 (Box 52)
      - Jones Beer Bike "License to Drink", 2007 (Box 52)
      - KrytoNOD "Horny Heroes and Villainous Vixens", 2008 (Box 52)
      - Candyland Study Break, 2009 (Box 52)
      - "Impact Rice Retreat" shirt, 2010 (Box 52)
      - 24th Annual AIA Sandcastle Competition at East Beach Galveston, Texas, June 5th, 2010 (Box 52)
      - South Asian Society "desi inside" t-shirt, 2010-2011 (Box 52)
      - North Colleges Block Party, April 20, 2012 (Box 52)
      - North Colleges Centennial Block Party, October 10, 2012 (Box 52)
      - "May the Odds be ever in your favor" Career & Internship Expo t-shirt, September 19, 2013 (Box 52)
      - North Colleges Block Party, November 15, 2013 (Box 52)
      - National Philanthropy Week, 2013 (Box 52)
      - Gumball Challenge, 2014 (Box 52)
      - National Philanthropy Week, 2014 (Box 52)
      - OWLCON t-shirt, 1980-02-22 (Box 52)
    - Undated Single Event T-shirts
      - "Contain yourself" 5th Annual Homecoming Tennis Tournament (Box 53)
      - Weiss Tabletop: "West Side Story" (Box 53)
      - "The Wizard of NOD" security shirt (Box 53)
      - "The Wonderful World of Nod" t-shirt (Box 53)
      - Grey Rice Summit T-Shirt, n.d. (Box 53)
      - Blue Rice Summit T-shirt (Box 53)
      - Wizard Movie - Unnatural Pursuits, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology at Rice University Events
      - Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology at Rice University "Tunafest" t-shirt, 2004 (Box 53)
      - Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology at Rice University "Tunafest" t-shirt, 2005 (Box 53)
      - Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology at Rice University "Tunafest" t-shirt, 2007 (Box 53)
      - Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology at Rice University "Sus-Tuna-bility" t-shirt, 2008 (Box 53)
      - Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology at Rice University "Tuna-finity and Beyond" t-shirt, 2011 (Box 53)
    - Orientation Week
      - Acapulco Jones Tour Guide O-week, 1987 (Box 53)
      - Baker Believe "U.F.O. Week: the Mother Ship has Landed" t-shirt, 1999 (Box 53)
      - White Jones "Best O-week ever" t-shirt, 2006 (Box 53)
      - Blue O-Week outreach, 2010 (Box 53)
      - Gray Campus-Wide O-Week, 2011 (Box 53)
      - Campus-wide O-week, 2011 (Box 53)
      - Pink Campus-Wide O-Week, 2012 (Box 53)
      - Blue Campus-wide O-week t-shirt, 2012 (Box 53)
      - Orientation Week t-shirt belonging to Katherine M., 2013 (Box 53)
      - White O-week t-shirt, 2016 (Box 53)
    - Owl Days
      - Owl Weekend, 1999 (Box 54)
      - Owl weekend t-shirt, 2000 (Box 54)
      - Rice University Owl Weekend, 2001 (Box 54)
      - Gray Owl Weekend t-shirt, 2003 (Box 54)
      - White Owl Weekend t-shirt, 2003 (Box 54)
      - Owl Days, 2009 (Box 54)
      - White Owl Days, 2010 (Box 54)
    - Vision t-shirts
      - Black Rice University Vision t-shirt, February 24-27th, 2000 (Box 54)
      - White Vision t-shirt, February 24-27, 2000 (Box 54)
      - White Rice University Vision t-shirt, 2001 (Box 54)
      - Blue Rice University Vision t-shirt, February 22-25, 2001 (Box 54)
      - Blue Rice University Vision t-shirt, 2002 (Box 54)
      - White Vision t-shirt, 2002 (Box 54)
      - White Rice University Vision t-shirt, 2004 (Box 54)
      - Gray Vision t-shirt, 2004 (Box 54)
      - White Rice University Vision t-shirt, 2005 (Box 54)
      - Blue Vision t-shirt, 2005 (Box 54)
    - Welcome Back Days
      - Welcome Back Day, 2012 (Box 54)
      - Navy Welcome Back Day t-shirt, 2014 (Box 54)
      - Turquoise Welcome Back Day t-shirt, 2014 (Box 54)
      - Welcome Back Day, 2015 (Box 54)
  - Sports T-shirts
    - Homecoming Shirts
      - White "Rice vs. University of Houston" Football Homecoming t-shirt, 1995 (Box 55)
      - White "Rice Homecoming" t-shirt with flags, 1990 (Box 55)
      - White "Rice vs. SMU" Homecoming t-shirt, November 4, 2000 (Box 55)
      - White "Beat Tulsa" Homecoming t-shirt with navy blue collar and sleeve cuffs, 2003 (Box 55)
    - Intramural Sports
      - Jones Powderpuff, 2005 (Box 55)
      - Rice Quidditch Team, 2013 (Box 55)
      - Rice Lacrosse, n.d. (Box 55)
    - NCAA College World Series Baseball Championships
      - White NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 1997 (Box 55)
      - White NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 1997 (Box 55)
      - Blue NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 1998 (Box 55)
      - Gray 50th Anniversary NCAA Omaha College World Series, 1999 (Box 55)
      - Gray NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 2001 (Box 55)
      - Blue NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 2002 (Box 55)
      - Gray NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 2003 (Box 55)
      - Blue NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 2003 (Box 55)
      - White NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 2003 (Box 55)
      - White NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 2003 (Box 55)
      - White NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 2003 (Box 55)
      - White NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 2003 (Box 55)
      - White NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 2003 (Box 55)
      - White NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 2003 (Box 55)
      - Gray NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 2007 (Box 55)
      - Blue NCAA Division I Baseball Championship College World Series, 2007 (Box 55)
      - White Rice "Back 2 Back" Baseball Championships (Box 55)
    - South West Conference Baseball Champions
      - Gray Rice Baseball SWC Champions t-shirt, 1994 (Box 56)
      - White Rice Baseball SWC Champions t-shirt, 1996 (Box 56)
    - Sporting Events
      - 2nd Annual Rice Sports Carnival, September 17, 1995 (Box 56)
      - 5th Annual Rice Sports Carnival, September 20, 1998 (Box 56)
      - Blue t-shirt "Tuck Fexas", September 20, 2003 (Box 56)
      - Basketball "Halloween Hoops" t-shirt, 2003 (Box 56)
      - White Basketball "Jungle Gym Jam" t-shirt, 2003 (Box 56)
      - Blue Football t-shirt New Orleans Bowl, December 22, 2006 (Box 56)
      - White Football t-shirt New Orleans Bowl, December 22, 2006 (Box 56)
      - Rice vs. Navy t-shirt, n.d. (Box 56)
      - Men's Basketball Chinese New Year Tank Top (Box 56)
      - Margaritaville Night at the Ballpark, n.d. (Box 56)
    - Generic Sports Shirts
      - "Stepping out for the Owls" Rice Women's Athletics t-shirt, 1992 (Box 56)
      - "Stepping out for the Owls" Rice Women's Athletics t-shirt, 1993 (Box 56)
      - Rice University "Take me out to the ball park" Baseball shirt, 2010s (Box 56)
      - Rice University Baseball shirt (Box 56)
      - Friends of Rice Athletics "Uncle Sammy Needs You" (Box 56)
      - Yellow "Rice A6A 26" shirt (Box 56)
      - Gray Rice University Athletic Department t-shirt, n.d. (Box 56)
      - Gray t-shirt with Chinese characters and the number 17 (Box 56)
      - Autry's Army, n.d. (Box 56)
      - Gray t-shirt with state of Texas with baseball lacings and R (Box 56)
      - "Dig for the Cause" volleyball t-shirt, n.d. (Box 56)
      - "White Out" t-shirt, n.d. (Box 56)
      - Rice Soccer tank top, n.d. (Box 56)
      - Gray Rice Soccer t-shirt, n.d. (Box 56)
  - Student Life T-shirts
    - Ideological T-shirts
      - "I am not Homophobic" t-shirt, n.d. (Box 57)
      - "Rice for Choice" t-shirt with a blue gavel, n.d. (Box 57)
      - University Anti-Stigma Campaign, 2011 (Box 57)
      - Women's Resource Center "This is what a Feminist looks like", n.d. (Box 57)
    - International University of Bremen t-shirt, ca. 1990s (Box 57)
    - "Rjce" "Have a nice elec day" t-shirt, 2005-2006 (Box 57)
    - "Bronano technology at Rice", n.d. (Box 57)